testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hi
Flover
How long has it been?
Since our concert
it's the first time
Flover
What were you doing?
You look pretty today
I was hungry so
I'm going to eat
a financier
Did you eat?
This is
yellow cheese
flavor
I'm hooked on it
After
the concert ended
I gained some weight
I gained a little weight so
I ate a bit less
again
You're asking where my cheek fat went?
You can't see it anymore
If I
gain weight on my cheeks
No because then
my stomach
gains weight too
So I can't
Should we talk about the concert?
How was the concert?
Flover
It was fun
Did my abs
appear in your dreams?
They did?
That's cute
You're saying you
made a GIF out of
my abs?
But
when I looked up that video
I actually had
a six-pack
I think it's pretty cool
But I don't have it right now
Hey who took this spot?
Maru is
and Hodu are
doing well actually
Today I
had a fansign
and at the fansign
I received Pokemon cards
so on live
I decided to unbox them
Honestly
I don't really know much about them
I don't know what's good
or which cards are good so are there any Flovers who know them well?
Press 1
I don't know them well
Ah there are so many
in here
If it's a good card
I heard it's super expensive
If I pull an expensive card
won't the Flover who gave this to me get super jealous?
Looking at the cards
I have to pull them without looking
I have to pull without looking
Any Flover who knows this well?
How about this? Is this good?
No? Got it
But wait
can I turn on a filter?
Thanks
I'll turn it on
Alright let's confidently unbox these cards
Here
what about
this one?
Is this
one good?
Oh wait why is there a good one at the back?
Got it
Hide it hide it
What is this one?
Is it good?
This
Jamming Tower
Xatu
Moonlit Hill
Hey
This is good
Is this good?
What is this?
Is this one good?
Is it good or bad? Got it what about this one?
What's this?
What is it?
Is it good?
How much is it?
What is it?
One million
How much?
One million won?
Got it
Okay
Then I'll put it in my wallet
Next
Now this one
Is it good?
Not good
Okay
This one is good
You say it sucks?
What about this?
It's not shiny?
Yeah
Not shiny
Yeah not shiny
Wait the one behind it is shiny what's this?
What is this?
Is it good?
What's this?
Not good? Skip it got it
What is this?
Not good
Got it
What about this one
This one
Shiny?
One million won?
What? You're saying it's similar?
I just earned two million won
Two million won
You're saying a one million won card comes out this easily?
Don't be fooled?
What's the truth then?
Tell me
the truth
No but really then
how much is it?
How much?
How much is it?
How much is this?
I'll move on to
the next one
Oh this
this one
It's heavy
Is this good?
Not good
This looks good
It looks good
This really looks good
Got it
This is good
Okay I'll set this aside too
This is so cute
How much is this one?
I don't know what's real anymore
Ah it's cute
It has sparkles
Chien-Pao
Behind it
this one
This is good
It's gold
This one
Is this good?
Why is
why is
this good?
Three million won?
Two million won?
Really?
How much is it
What is this?
This?
Is this really good?
Terapagos
Is this good?
You're saying I shouldn't scratch it? Got it
No but if it's this easy to pull
I just
earned like five million won right now
If they come out this easily
wouldn't everyone just buy this?
But I bet they're all
lying right?
How about this?
I guess the good ones come out at the end
This one
how about this?
Doesn't look good right?
Got it
Moving to
the next one
Why is this so fun?
This is good
What is it?
Not good?
What about
this one?
Did this come out earlier?
I see
Next
I'll set this aside
How about this?
This this
This is
a dud
Gold is the best
Here I go
It's cute
What is this?
No?
It's cute though
This one
Oh this really looks good
What is this?
What is it?
For now
I'll set it aside
Raging
Bolt
Oh
a good one
must have come out
How about this one?
Skip it
This one
How about this?
Should I set this aside?
I'll set it aside
This one
this
Set it aside
This is
Palafin
This looks good
For now
I'll set it aside
This is the last one
The last one
Wow what is this? It's already
been almost
20 minutes
I thought it would end quickly
Oh
So cute
It's cute so I'll set it aside
What is this?
Hey
Okay
What is this?
No?
Not good
What is this?
Is it good?
It's a dud
Gold is the best
Now I'll show you
the ones
I set aside
I earned five million won you know
This one
is cute so
I set it aside
This one
And this
three million won one
This one million won one
One million won
How is it?
I earned so much today
I'm rich
I've become rich
But
honestly I
don't really know
these things well
But
Pokemon cards are trending these days
so I received them at the fansign
and it was really
fun
It was fascinating
But
there are so many Pokemon cards
Yeah what is this anyway?
What is this?
I'll set them aside separately
This
and this
Three million won
Is it really three million won?
No?
Well I had fun
so
it's
fine
I felt good for a moment
It was fun
Flover
Was the concert fun this time?
How was the concert?
For this concert
somehow
the Flovers
who came to the fansign
and on Fromm too
they were telling me
that it was the most fun concert
they've seen so far
I heard that a lot
Maybe that's why
I don't know if that's why
but even before hearing that
somehow
I also
thought this concert
was so so
good and
the most fun
The setlist
was good
What else was good?
Your eye contact
was good
The screen time was good
Hayoung
looking at me
with that gaze
was funny
Wasn't starting with Rewind so good?
Rewind
at this concert
on day one
wasn't it really good?
Somehow
Okay
after the last chorus
we walk backwards
and that kind of directing
itself was really good
Somehow
being able to show
various directing
and stages
was really really good
This time with the directing
team as well
we had lots of conversations
and
the directing
team
had so much
affection
for us
so we also
thought more about what we wanted to do
and what Flover
would
like
and
filled it with those kind of stages
Also
the encore stage
we did it right
For me
this time
we performed all ten songs
from the full
length
we performed all ten songs
album
But
I knew you'd like those songs too of course
I actually thought you'd like them a bit more
but Flovers
reacted so well
to our older songs
when we performed them
So
when Flovers
heard
our existing songs
the older ones
they must have felt
that touching feeling
and those
emotions
coming all at once
So
it was so good
that I cried
Wow
that part was good
When I was singing
facing Jiwon
at that time
the feeling is different
when singing it during practice
compared to singing it on stage
When singing it
during practice
just looking at each other
makes us laugh
but singing it
on stage
means singing it in front of Flover
So it feels really affectionate
and the exact moment
we are singing it
feels like a scene from a movie
It was like that
It really was
Prom
Prom was good too
Listening to Prom makes you tear up a bit right?
It's a special point
for both Flovers and the members
And when Flovers
sang along to Prom it was so good
Your voices were so beautiful
Blind Letter
was good too
Blind Letter and
Attitude and
also
showing a new side of us
was really good
Cold Blooded too
This song
really
Eternal
the ad-libs
for Eternal
Originally Eternal
didn't have
ad-libs
But
I created
the ad-libs for Eternal
So
somehow
we could enjoy it
with a richer sound
which was really good
The digital version of
this
song Eternal
is a bit
overwhelming
and raises
your emotions
it's that kind of song
so it matched
well
with that vibe
burning
up
even more
like that
so I added it in
It's already been
30 minutes
I need to wash up and sleep
Should I just
do 5 more minutes?
Flover but
do you remember
when I said
not to feel empty
at the concert?
But even though I told you not to feel empty I
felt a bit empty
I felt a bit empty
I missed you
Somehow
when I'm on stage
Flovers
shine
so brightly on us right
So
when that time passes
that time itself
really
feels like a dream
Oh and that
phrase in the intro
that goes 'a dream I want to dream again'
Did you know I'm the one
who said that?
A dream I want to dream again
That's what
I told Flover
The lyricist saw that
and put it in
Don't you think
they have great
sense?
A dream I want to dream
again
I really think
the concert itself
feels like a dream I want to dream again
Now that it's over wow
it feels like a dream
Is it a dream?
Was it a dream?
I keep thinking like that
And
I
really
wondered if
it was a dream
I
did it
28 times
you know
It's so funny that a Flover counted that 28 times
A Flover
even uploaded
the full version
of that
So I
was watching it
and it was so funny
You want me
to do agungppang?
My eyes don't match right now
I don't think it's working well
It's a bit
not pretty
Pretty?
My hair length is about this long right now
and it just
won't grow past this point
This length
is
what people call
the beggar zone
I keep wanting to cut it at this length
I think I know why
people
keep maintaining
this length
Sorry
Hey Hodu
Hey Hodudol do you not want
any screen time?
Hmm?
Stay in mom's arms
then
Ah but really
the concert was so good
Want me to show you something funny?
It flew away
It just flew away
Flover gave
me this too
They told me to expose my bangs
but it hurts
And
between this
Both passed?
Flovers who say both
are correct
It's purring so much
Yeah
Purring cat
Did you watch
Bangpan Girls?
Bangpan
really
I've gotten
close to the writer
and PD now
We've become close
I'm not doing
what I want to do
but what they want to do
I'm just doing what they tell me to
Those people
Shall we watch the challenge
with Hodu?
Hodu can
do it
Yeah
Got it
I want to do the Chicken Banana challenge
Hodu
Chicken
down
Should I show Flovers
the Chicken Banana after a long time?
Chicken
Bana
Ah nice
But Hodu really likes it
Can you hear the purring?
Want me to let you hear the purring?
You heard it right?
Hodu is liking it right now
What is it? Hodu you really like it right?
Just doing what you like
Chicken
Yes
Where is it?
I can't understand
you purring
while hating it
You're just
I should really
play with our Hodu
Come here
Hodu
Duduk
Our Hodu sometimes
goes by Dudu
Holong
Tudu
has so many names
As for Maru
where is Maru?
Maru
Where did Maru go?
Maru come
here
Come here
Maru
Here
Not coming
quickly
won't come right?
Maru is
lying on the chair right now
and has no thoughts of getting up
Hodol
You're such
a cutie
It's a bit much
Why are you acting so cute?
Why are you in such a good mood right now?
Give it here
Yeah
Give it
Hodu if you feel good
make some noise
If you feel
good
make some noise
Should I go now?
Maru if you come
I'll do exactly 5 more minutes and turn it off
If you don't come
I'll go now
Come up right now
Right
now
Maru
Maru you
like this blanket right?
Maru
Maru is here
Oh oh you hate it you hate it
I'll stay a little longer
Let's go until 50 minutes
Because
for tomorrow
I need to sleep
No I really meant to do just 10 minutes
and thought 10 minutes then washing up and sleeping would be perfect
Time goes
faster
than I thought
They say
time really flies
when you're
having fun
Flover
when we do
a concert
honestly
I
don't really watch concerts well
But if you know a lot of songs
it's really nice
So
that's why I told Flovers
to listen
to the songs
a lot
because anyway Flovers need to know the songs
for the concert to be fun right
So
I told you to listen to them a lot
You have to know the songs
to have fun and enjoy it together
Next time
we do a concert
you have to listen to the songs a lot
before coming
Got it?
It's really fun when you know the songs
Flover today
was fun
Time goes so fast and the concert
time went really fast too
But didn't time fly for this concert?
During the concert
it felt like
we just started but then
we were suddenly doing the final greeting
didn't it?
It's a time thief
Flover's
own
time thief
I was really happy
Since it's an Asia tour now
I'll do my best
until the very end of the tour
I think it'll be so fun
Somehow
I'm looking forward to it
because of the setlist
and everything this time
A little bit
when we go to other countries
for the tour
there might be
some
changes
just a little
but we'll still keep it
somewhat similar
and take this with us
so
I think it'll be so fun
It'll be happy
It's almost Chuseok now
Flover
we reached
1 million hearts
Capture time
Nice
Good job
Thanks so much
for hanging out with me
until this late tonight
Ah the hearts
Thanks for pressing hearts so much
Don't your hands hurt?
Stretch your hands well
Stretch them well
and let's sleep tight
Got it?
Today too
I'll be going now
Come up
Great job
Bye
Good night